Website LinkedIn GitHub vohoangviet459@gmail.com +84 921.000.869 Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

Front end web developer with 3+ years of teamwork experience in management and customer service who aspires to convey people skills to tech, explore new technologies and develop amazing websites.

PROJECTS

- vietspace.me My interactive & responsive portfolio.
 Skills: HTML + CSS Flexbox, animation & transition + JavaScript.
- <u>Soundwave Music Player</u> Minimal music player visualizes audio with random background feature. Skills: HTML + CSS + JavaScript ES6 + REST APIs.
- Side project I'm working on: Saigon Cribs Real estate website built on WordPress with Advanced Custom Fields.

SKILLS

- Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6 & React.
- CMS: WordPress.
- Version Control: Git, GitHub.
- Design: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Adobe XD, Figma, Canva.
- Latest working tools: VS Code, GitHub, Google Ads, Analytics, Tag Manager, Salesforce.

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

TDCX November 2021 - Present

- Have instructed 65+ advertisers to successfully set up and implement Google Ads conversion tracking via Google
 Tag Manager. Simplified technical concepts and delivered detailed instructions.
- Guide advertisers on understanding Ads conversions, Analytics reports and optimizing campaigns.
- Review and provide on time troubleshooting on website issues via Google Meet.
- Customize JavaScript code for data layers tracking and implementation.
- Manage tasks and workflow via Salesforce.

Front End Development Student

Skillcrush July 2021 - November 2021

- Built 3 mobile responsive websites using HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript, transformed PSDs into pixel perfect templates.
- Deployed 5+ web applications using JavaScript / React.
- Produced 4 high fidelity design mockups using Adobe XD, Photoshop and Figma.
- Designed visual identity for a coffee brand using Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign.
- Supported fellow developers and designers on Slack community in debugging and building good design patterns.

Sales Executive

Loship March 2021 – May 2021

- Contributed 15% of monthly sales revenue by efficiently allocating time to meet customers and research new markets. Introduced delivery solution in a non-technical way and instructed customers to use Loship application to increase their sales.
- Developed a new market by collaborating with 21 new merchants. Helped customers build online presence to expand business reach.

Virtual Assistant to CEO

Saigon Cribs

November 2020 – March 2021

- Remotely organized and extended property database by 60%. Matched requests by understanding client's needs, following specifications and productive searching.
- Enhanced customer's satisfaction by reaching 3 5 day deadlines and negotiating with landlords to decrease price by 10% or provide more amenities.

EDUCATION